Finding Aid to the San Francisco Department of Public Health AIDS Office records SFH 4
San Francisco History Center, San Francisco Public Library
- Contracts and Related Documents, 1984-1993; Record Group 2; 39 Cubic Feet
  - Requests for Proposals (RFPs), Series 12
    - RFP 112-91: CARE: First RFP
      - Miscellaneous Proposals (Box 25, Folder 18)
      - Title I Supplemental: St. Mary's Outpatient Care (Box 25, Folder 19)
      - Review Instructions, SErvice Priorities, Review Teams (Box 25, Folder 20)
      - Review Team Scoring; Primary Medical Care (Box 25, Folder 21)
      - Review Team Scoring; Other Services (Box 25, Folder 22)
      - Drafts of CARE Award Letters (Box 25, Folder 23)
      - Awards-Original Confidential List (Box 25, Folder 24)
      - Awards-Lists Distributed to Public (Box 25, Folder 25)
      - Press Conference, February 21, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 26)
      - Award Package for Public Review (Box 25, Folder 27)
      - Supplemental Recommendations (Box 25, Folder 28)
      - Various Award Lists & Analysis (Box 25, Folder 29)
      - Awards to Current Contractors (Box 25, Folder 30)
      - Awards to New Contractors (Box 25, Folder 31)
      - Applicants Wanting to Review Results (Box 25, Folder 32)
    - RFP 113-91: Prevention and Education in the Tenderloin
      - Bidders Conference (Box 26, Folder 1)
      - Community Meetings (Box 26, Folder 2)
      - Working Papers and Notes (Box 26, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence (Box 26, Folder 4)
      - Review (Box 26, Folder 5)
      - RFP Forms (Box 26, Folder 6)
      - HRC Forms (Box 26, Folder 7)
      - Tenderloin AIDS Resource Center Proposal (Box 26, Folder 8)
      - California Prostitutes Education Project (CAL-PEP) Proposal (Box 26, Folder 9)
      - Glide Foundation Proposal (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - RFP 118-91: Early Intervention & Resource Center (CPC)
      - Review: Final Selections Report (Box 26, Folder 11)
      - Community Meetings (Box 26, Folder 12)
      - Correspondence (Box 26, Folder 13)
      - Working Papers and Notes (Box 26, Folder 14)
      - Bidders Conference (Box 26, Folder 15)
      - Review Workpapers (Box 26, Folder 16)
      - Review Bidder & Award Analysis (Box 26, Folder 17)
      - RFP Forms (Box 26, Folder 18)
      - HRC Forms (Box 26, Folder 19)
      - Davies Medical Center Anticipated Proposal (Box 26, Folder 20)
      - Davies Withdrawal (Box 26, Folder 21)
      - UCSF AIDS Health Project Propsal (Box 26, Folder 22)
      - National Task Force on AIDS Prevention (NTFAP) Proposal (Box 26, Folder 23)
      - California Prosituties Education Project (CALPEP) Proposal (Box 26, Folder 24)
      - San Francisco AIDS Foundation Proposal (Box 26, Folder 25)
      - STOP AIDS Project Proposal (Box 26, Folder 26)
      - Catholic Charities / San Francisco County Proposal (Box 26, Folder 27)
      - Haight-Ashbury Free Clinic Proposal (Box 26, Folder 28)
    - RFP 136-91: Prevention and Education Media Services Targeting Closeted Men of Color (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - RFP 139-91: CARE Proposals
      - CARE Title II 91 (Box 27, Folder 2)
      - 2nd Notification Letters, April 23, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 3)
      - CARE Application Confidential until November 3, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 4)
      - HRC Forms (Box 27, Folder 5)
      - Community Information Meetings (Box 27, Folder 6)
      - Working Papers and Notes (Box 27, Folder 7)
      - Application Package (Box 27, Folder 8)
      - Advertisements (Box 27, Folder 9)
      - Review Lists (Box 27, Folder 10)
      - CARE 1992 One-Time Savings Augmentations (Box 27, Folder 11)
      - 3rd Notice Using Title II Money (Box 27, Folder 12)
      - Correspondence (Box 27, Folder 13)
      - Applicants to Review Results (Box 27, Folder 14)
      - Selection Committee Reports for Review (Box 27, Folder 15)
      - Selection Committee Reports Copies for Review (Box 27, Folder 16)
      - Selection Committee Reports, Originals (Box 27, Folder 17)
      - Substance Abuse Proposals (Box 27, Folder 18)
      - Primary Medical Proposals (Box 27, Folder 19)
      - Other Primary Health Proposals (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - Housing Proposals (Box 28, Folder 2)
      - Psychosocial Support Proposals (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - RFP 141-91: HIV Prevention and Education Media Advertising for Communities of Color
      - Bidders Conference (Box 28, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence (Box 28, Folder 5)
      - Working Papers and Notes (Box 28, Folder 6)
      - Review Report (Box 28, Folder 7)
      - RFP Forms (Box 28, Folder 8)
      - HRC Forms (Box 28, Folder 9)
      - RFP 142-91:
        - Bidders Conference (Box 28, Folder 10)
        - Correspondence (Box 28, Folder 11)
        - Working Papers and Notes (Box 28, Folder 12)
        - Review Report (Box 28, Folder 13)
        - RFP Forms (Box 28, Folder 14)
        - HRC Forms (Box 28, Folder 15)
        - Miscellaneous Papers (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - RFP 143-91:
    - RFP 144-91: HIV Prevention and Education for African-American Community
      - Bidders Conference (Box 28, Folder 17)
      - Working Papers and Notes (Box 28, Folder 18)
      - Correspondence (Box 28, Folder 19)
      - Review Report (Box 28, Folder 20)
      - RFP Forms (Box 28, Folder 21)
      - HRC Forms (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - RFP 145-91: Hospital Inpatient Counseling for People with AIDS
      - Bidders Conference (Box 29, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence (Box 29, Folder 2)
      - Working Papers and Notes (Box 29, Folder 3)
      - Review Report (Box 29, Folder 4)
      - RFP Forms (Box 29, Folder 5)
      - HRC Forms (Box 29, Folder 6)
      - Shanti Project Proposal (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - RFP 147-92: Prevention and Education for Gay and Bisexual Men--Relapse Services
      - Bidders Conference (Box 29, Folder 8)
      - Correspondence (Box 29, Folder 9)
      - Working Papers and Notes (Box 29, Folder 10)
      - Review Report (Box 29, Folder 11)
      - RFP Forms (Box 29, Folder 12)
      - HRC Forms (Box 29, Folder 13)
      - Review of Proposals Packet (Box 29, Folder 14)
      - San Francisco AIDS Foundation Proposal (Box 29, Folder 15-16)
    - RFP 148-92 and 149-92: CARE Services to be Provided by People of Color Community Based Organizations; and Services to be Provided to Youth, Ages 13-24
      - Bidders Conference (Box 29, Folder 17)
      - Correspondence (Box 29, Folder 18)
      - Working Papers and Notes (Box 29, Folder 19)
      - Review Report (Box 29, Folder 20)
      - RFP Forms (Box 29, Folder 21)
      - HRC Forms (Box 29, Folder 22)
      - Other Primary Health Review Documents (Box 29, Folder 23)
      - Substance Abuse Review Documents (Box 29, Folder 24)
      - Youth Substance Abuse and Housing (Box 29, Folder 25)
      - Proposals (Box 29, Folder 26)
    - RFP 164-92: HIV Prevention and Education for High Risk Latino Populations
      - Bidders Conference (Box 29, Folder 27)
      - Correspondence (Box 29, Folder 28)
      - Working Papers and Note (Box 29, Folder 29)
      - Review Report (Box 29, Folder 30)
      - RFP Forms (Box 29, Folder 31)
      - Instituto Familiar de la Raza Proposal (Box 29, Folder 32)
      - Coalition for Immigrant and Refugee Rights and Services Proposal (Box 29, Folder 33)
      - Horizons Unlimited of San Francisco Proposal (Box 29, Folder 34)
    - RFP 165-92: HIV Prevention and Education for Latino Gay and Bisexual Men, 1992
      - Correspondence (Box 29, Folder 35)
      - Review Report (Box 29, Folder 36)
      - RFP Forms (Box 29, Folder 37)
      - Bidders Conference (Box 29, Folder 38)
      - Working Papers and Notes (Box 29, Folder 39)
      - Comunidad Unida en Respuesta al SIDA (CURA) Proposal (Box 29, Folder 40)
      - Coalition for Immigrant and Refugee Rights and Services Proposal (Box 29, Folder 41)
    - RFP 166-92: HIV Prevention & Education for African American High Risk Populations
      - Bidders Conference (Box 30, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence (Box 30, Folder 2)
      - Working Papers and Notes (Box 30, Folder 3)
      - Review Report (Box 30, Folder 4)
      - RFP Forms (Box 30, Folder 5)
      - Bayview Hunters Point Foundation Proposal (Box 30, Folder 6)
      - CAL-PEP Proposal (Box 30, Folder 7)
      - California AIDS Intervention Training Center (CAITC) Proposal (Box 30, Folder 8)
      - Multicultural Training Resource Center Proposal (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - RFP 167-92: HIV Prevention and Needle Exchange Services for Injection Drug Users
      - Bidders Conference (Box 30, Folder 10)
      - Correspondence (Box 30, Folder 11)
      - Working Papers and Notes (Box 30, Folder 12)
      - Review Report (Box 30, Folder 13)
      - Review of Proposals Packet (Box 30, Folder 14)
      - RFP Forms (Box 30, Folder 15)
      - San Francisco AIDS Foundation Proposal (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - RFP 171-92: Street Outreach Prevention to High Risk Youth (AESOP)
      - Bidders Conference (Box 30, Folder 17)
      - Correspondence (Box 30, Folder 18)
      - Working Papers and Notes (Box 30, Folder 19)
      - Review Report (Box 30, Folder 20)
      - Review of Proposals Packet (Box 30, Folder 21)
      - RFP Forms (Box 30, Folder 22)
      - HRC Forms (Box 30, Folder 23)
      - Haight-Ashbury Free Clinics Proposal (Box 30, Folder 24)
    - RFP 016-93: Psychosocial Support Services
      - Bidders Conference (Box 30, Folder 25)
      - Review (Box 30, Folder 26)
      - Kommunities of Kolor United Against AIDS (KOKUA) Partial Proposal (Box 30, Folder 27)
      - San Francisco AIDS Foundation Proposal (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - Contracts, Series 13
    - Bayview Hunters Point Foundation: AIAI (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - American Indian AIDS Institute of San Francisco (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - FY 1990-91 BVHP Foundation: CT83-17010 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Black Coalition on AIDS:
      - CT83-00317 (Box 31, Folder 4)
      - CT83-00334 (Box 31, Folder 5)
      - CT83-00319 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - California Public Health Foundation 83-07045 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - California Public Health Foundation PCR Testing (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - CAL-PEP: Contract In Process (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Catholic Charities: GF/STATE/RAS CT83-00312,07008 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - AIDS Health Project: Education and Social Support Services (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - AIDS Health Project: Education Support CT83-00330 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - UCSF: Urban Health Study: Urban Health Study (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Westside Community Mental Health Center (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Women's Institute for Mental Health (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Women's Institute for Mental Health CT-83-07035 (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - Youth Environment Study (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - CSEARR (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - CURAS Contract (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - CURAS CT83-10332 (Box 31, Folder 20-21)
    - 118th Street Services (Box 31, Folder 22)
    - ENE (Box 31, Folder 23)
    - ENE: GF/STATE/CDC (Box 31, Folder 24)
    - Shanti Support Services and Training
      - Contract CT 83-72017 (Box 32, Folder 1)
      - Contract Modification, CT 83-72025 A (Box 32, Folder 2)
      - Contract CT 83-71204 (Box 32, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - 18th Street Services, 87/88: Education for IVDUs Contract Modification CT 83-72025A (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - PPMC,87/88 Home Health Care
      - Contract (Box 32, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence & Monitoring Report (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Asian American Recovery Services, 87/88
      - Contract CT 83-72039 (Box 32, Folder 8)
      - Correspondence (Box 32, Folder 9)
      - Contract Ad Val CT 83-71205 (Box 32, Folder 10)
      - Contract Ad Val CT 83-71206 (Box 32, Folder 11)
      - Contract State CT 83-72016 (Box 32, Folder 12)
      - Contract Fed HRSA CT 83-72018 (Box 32, Folder 13)
      - Contract Processing Docs (Box 32, Folder 14)
      - Correspondence (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - John Hayes, Consultant Contract CT 83-71202 (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - SFAF, 87/88 Education Services
      - Contract CT 83-71202 (Box 32, Folder 17)
      - Contract CT 83-72002 (Box 32, Folder 18)
      - Contract CT 83-72003 (Box 32, Folder 19)
      - Contract CT 83-72003 A (Box 32, Folder 20)
      - Contract CT 83-72004 (Box 32, Folder 21)
      - Contract Contract Review (Box 32, Folder 22)
      - Correspondence (Box 32, Folder 23)
    - Prevention
      - Asian Amer IDth Forum/AIPCA, 90/91 CT83-00316 (Box 32, Folder 24)
      - Asian Amer IDth ForumIFTFA, 90/91 CT83-07049 (Box 32, Folder 25)
      - Asian Amer Recovery Serv. 90/91 CT83-07075 (Box 32, Folder 26)
      - BVHPF, 90/91 CT83-07047 (Box 32, Folder 27)
      - ENE Advertising, 90/91 CT83-07060-6 (Box 32, Folder 28)
      - Genesis Church TAN, 90/91 CT83-00307, 10323 (Box 32, Folder 29)
      - Haight Ashbury, 90/91 CT83-94102A (Box 32, Folder 30)
    - Health Services
      - Black Coalition On AIDS, 90/91 CT83-0017 (Box 32, Folder 31)
      - Black Coalition On AIDS, 90/91 CT83-00319 (Box 32, Folder 32)
      - Catholic Charities, 90/91 CT83-00312 (Box 32, Folder 33)
    - Prevention & Health Services CURAS, 90/91 CT83-07088, 07089, 07027A & B (Box 32, Folder 34)
    - San Francisco Aids Foundation/EIRC Clinical Trials, CT83-10348, GF (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - San Francisco Aids Foundation/EIRC, CT83-10330, GF (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - San Francisco Aids Foundation/CAL-PEP, CT83-10327A, GF (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Support Center, CT83-17403, CARE-STATE
      Missing Material
      This file is listed in the legacy finding aid but is missing from the box.
    - Mission Neighborhood Health Center:
      - CT83-00304, GF/STATE (Box 33, Folder 4)
      - CT83-07003, STATE & GF (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Black and White Men Together. NTFA / GMCC / EACH: CM83-00306A, 00306, 90313A. GF (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Pacific Presbyterian Medical Center/Operation Concern: CT83-00322, GF (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - St. Mary's Hospital, CT83-07039, HRSA (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - San Francisco AIDS Foundation:
      - CT83-00326, GF (Box 33, Folder 9)
      - CT83-00339, 10328 (Box 33, Folder 10)
      - CT83-00341 (Box 33, Folder 11)
      - CT83-07005 (Box 33, Folder 12)
      - CT83-07021 (Box 33, Folder 13)
      - CT83-07079, CDC (Box 33, Folder 14)
      - CT83-90316,00303, GF/CDC/St Blk Grant (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - UCSF AIDS Health Project / Prevention & Education, CT83-07145, CM 83-94032A, GF/CDC/HRSA (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Women's Institute Mental Health, CT83-07035 (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - Catholic Charities, CT83-17036 (Box 33, Folder 18)
      - 24 Dementia Care, CT83-00333 (Box 33, Folder 19)
      - Attendant Care, CT83-07111 (Box 33, Folder 20)
      - Rita da Cascia, CT83-07113 (Box 33, Folder 21-22)
    - Central City Hospitality House, CT83-17051 (Box 33, Folder 23)
    - CURAS:
      - CT83-17045 (Box 33, Folder 24)
      - CT83-17009 (Box 33, Folder 25)
      - CT83-10342 (Box 33, Folder 26-27)
      - CT83-10332, CT83-10349 (Box 33, Folder 28)
    - Family Service Agency, CT83-07144 (Box 33, Folder 29)
    - Filipino Task Force on AIDS, CT83-10341 (Box 33, Folder 30)
    - Operation Branch: Contracts, 1987-1991; Subseries 13.1
      - 89/90 Asian American Recovery Services (Box 34, Folder 1)
      - 90/91 AAHF/GAPA, #83-00316 (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - Genesis Church, #83-00307 (Box 34, Folder 3)
      - Haight-Ashbury Clinic / CDC-IVDU HIV Couns/Test (89/90) (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - Shanti Project, CT#83-00301 (Box 34, Folder 5)
      - Shanti Project, CT#83-00321A (Box 34, Folder 6)
      - Instituto Familiar de La Raza, CT#83-94010 (Box 34, Folder 7)
      - UCSF AIDS Health Project / Prevention and Education, CT#83-00342, CM#83-94100A (Box 34, Folder 8)
      - Regents DC: CT#83-94100, CT#83-94046, CT#83-94013, CT#83-90306 (Box 34, Folder 9)
      - PPMC / Visiting Nurses & Hospice, CT 83-00320 (Box 34, Folder 10)
      - PPMC / Visiting Nurses & Hospice, CT 83-07050 (Box 34, Folder 11)
      - Mission Neighborhood Health Center, CT83-00304 (Box 34, Folder 12)
      - Operation Concern, CT 83-07108 (Box 34, Folder 13)
      - Contract Monitoring 87-88 (Box 34, Folder 14)
      - AIDS Health Project, ATS: MH - Ad Valorem (Box 34, Folder 15)
      - AIDS Health Project, Fed. PHS/HRSA (Box 34, Folder 16)
      - Asian American Recovery Service (AARS), Fed. PHS / HRSA (Box 34, Folder 17)
      - San Francisco AIDS Foundation (SFAF), Education - Ad Valorem (Box 34, Folder 18)
      - San Francisco AIDS Foundation, Social Services (Box 34, Folder 19)
      - Shanti Project: Ad Valorem (Box 34, Folder 20)
      - Polaris R &: PHS/HRSA 276 (Box 34, Folder 21)
      - Home Health Care, Ad Valorem (Box 34, Folder 22)
      - AIDS:SFDPH: SAMRA Center Suppl., 1987 RB (Box 34, Folder 23)
      - Instituto Familiar de la Raza, Ad Valorem (Box 34, Folder 24)
      - AIDS:SFDPH: Contracts (Box 34, Folder 25-36)
      - Summary of Contracts and General Fund Line Item Budges (Box 34, Folder 37)
      - Work Flow Charts (Box 34, Folder 38)
      - Signed Memorandum of Understanding (Box 34, Folder 39)
      - Service Priorities (Box 34, Folder 40)
      - CARE Title II Grant Application (Box 34, Folder 41)
      - Early Intervention Service Network Demonstration Project Grant Application (Box 34, Folder 42)
      - State Prevention Grant Audit (Box 34, Folder 43)
      - AIDS Services for Women (Box 34, Folder 44)
      - Y.E.S. Contract (Box 34, Folder 45)
      - Budget Available for Men-to-Men Prevention (Box 34, Folder 46)
      - C.A.R.E. Application (Box 34, Folder 47)
      - Catholic Charities, Peter Claver House Contract (Box 34, Folder 48)
      - AIDS Program Funding Summary (Box 34, Folder 49)
      - DPH Grants (Box 34, Folder 50)
      - Budget for Health Services (Box 34, Folder 51)
      - Schedule & Amounts for Requests for Proposals (Box 34, Folder 52)
      - Grant Application to CDC for ATS (Box 34, Folder 53)
    - Operations Branch: Contracts, 1991-1992; Subseries 13.2
      - AIDS Indigent Direct Services. 83-17031. CARE II (Box 35)
      - AIDS Indigent Direct Services: EIRC. 83-10310. GF (Box 35)
      - AIDS Indigent Direct Services: Lang Care. 83-07115. CARE I(A) (Box 35)
      - Asian American Health Forum. 83-17040. CARE II (Box 35)
      - Asian American Health Forum: APICA. 83-17004/10320A. GF&CDC (Box 35)
      - Asian American Health Forum: GAPA Case Mgmt. 83-07143. CARE I(B) (Box 35)
      - Bayview-Hunters Point Foundation 83-07137 CARE I(B) (Box 35)
      - Bayview-Hunters Point Foundation AlAI Prevo (Box 35)
      - Bayview-Hunters Point Foundation 83-10335 GF (Box 35)
      - Bayview-Hunters Point Foundation 83-00338/10305 GF (Box 35)
      - Bayview-Hunters Point Foundation AlAI Case Mgmt. 83-07092 CARE I(A) (Box 35)
      - Bayview-Hunters Point Foundation 83-17039 CARE II (Box 35)
      - Bayview-Hunters Point Foundation 18th Youth Proj. 83-10335,07155 STATE (Box 35)
      - Bayview-Hunters Point Foundation 18th IDDs 83-10346 GF (Box 35)
      - Bayview-Hunters Point Foundation EIRC 83-10339 GF (Box 35)
      - Black Coalition On AIDS 83-10311,10312 GF (Box 35)
      - CAL-PEP 83-00331,10301 GF (Box 35)
      - California Pacific Medical Center: O.C./Youth 83-10344,07154B TATE (Box 35)
      - California Pacific Medical Center: VNH / Hospice 83-17012-13 HRSA (Box 35)
      - California Pacific Medical Center: 83-17026S,17030 STATE & CARE II (Box 35)
      - Central City Hospitality House: Youth (Box 35)
      - C.U.R.A.S.: Case Mgmt. 83-07141 CAREI(B) (Box 35)
      - C.U.R.A.S.: Previous 83-10342,17009 GF&CDC (Box 35)
      - C.U.R.A.S.: EIRC/CFC 83-10332 GF (Box 35)
      - C.U.R.A.S.: Case Management 83-17045 STATE (Box 35)
      - Filipino Task Force On AIDS/GCHP 83-10341,A GF (Box 35)
      - Genesis Church/Ecumenical Center: Previous 83-10323,A GF (Box 35)
      - Genesis Church / Ecumenical Center: P-S Support 83-07097 CARE I (A) (Box 35)
      - Haight Ashbury Free Clinics EIRC 83-10309 GF (Box 35)
      - Hartford Zen Center: Hospice 83-07146 CARE I (B) (Box 35)
      - Health Outreach Team:Case Management 83-07106 CARE I (A) (Box 35)
      - Hispanic Headquarters Adv.: Prev/CURAS 83-10322,010322B GF (Box 35)
      - Instituto Familiar de La Raza 83-07090, A CARE I (A) (Box 35)
      - Larkin Street Youth Council 83-07090,A CARE I(B) (Box 35)
      - Mission Neighborhood Health Center: Clinic Advert. 83-17017,10314, A, GF, STATE EIP (Box 35)
      - National Association of Black and White Men Together (NABWMT) (BAHSES) 83-07091 CARE I (A) (Box 35)
      - NABWMT 83-10324,A GF (Box 35)
    - Operations Branch: Contracts, 1983-1992; Subseries 13.3
      - Appropriation Carry-forwards, August, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 1)
      - A/O Work Orders - Gen Fund, 1991-1992 (Box 36, Folder 2)
      - PEAT MARWICK AUDIT (Box 36, Folder 3)
      - STATE BLOCK GRANT, 1990-1991 (Box 36, Folder 4)
      - DPH: Budget Committee, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 5)
      - DPH: Budget Reductions, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 6)
      - SFC & C Financial Committee, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 7)
      - GF Supplemental, 1991-1992 (Box 36, Folder 8)
      - Beilenson Hearing for Budget, 1991-1992 (Box 36, Folder 9)
      - City Budget, 1991-1992 (Box 36, Folder 10)
      - City Budget-Community Input, 1991-1992 (Box 36, Folder 11)
      - City Supplemental Budget, 1990-1991 (Box 36, Folder 12)
      - G.F. Budget, 1991-1992 (Box 36, Folder 13)
      - HIV+ Planning (Box 36, Folder 14)
      - Units of Service (Box 36, Folder 15)
      - Fed & State AIDS Activities, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 16)
      - Request For Proposals, 1989-1990 (Box 36, Folder 17)
      - AIDS Prev Follow-up Cntr Prog (APFC), 1988 (Box 36, Folder 18)
      - AIDS Prev Follow-up Cntr Prog (APFC), January-June, 1989 (Box 36, Folder 19)
      - AIDS Prev Follow-up Cntr Prog (APFC), July 1989 - July 1990 (Box 36, Folder 20)
      - NABWMT HIV Minority Advocacy Proposal (Box 36, Folder 21)
      - MNHC APFC, August 1990-August 1991 (Box 36, Folder 22)
      - MBOs: Performance Assessment, 1986-1987 (Box 36, Folder 23)
      - Current Service Projections: Correspondence (Box 36, Folder 24-25)
      - Current Service Projections, Units of Service Index, 1986-1987 (Box 36, Folder 26)
      - MBOs: Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 36, Folder 27)
      - MBOs: Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 36, Folder 28)
      - MBOs: Quarterly Reports, 1985-1986 (Box 36, Folder 29)
      - MBOs: Performance Assessment, 1985-1986 (Box 36, Folder 30)
      - MBOs: Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 36, Folder 31)
      - MBOs: Quarterly Reports, 1984-1985 (Box 36, Folder 32)
      - MBOs: Performance Assessment, 1984-1985 (Box 36, Folder 33)
      - MBOs: Quarterly Reports, 1983-1984 (Box 36, Folder 34)
      - MBOs: Performance Assessments, 1983-1984 (Box 36, Folder 35)
    - Operations Branch: Contracts, 1990-1991; Subseries 13.4
      - AIDS New Contract Check List (Box 37, Folder 1)
      - Asian American Health Forum: CT83-07049 (Box 37, Folder 2)
      - Asian American Recovery Services: CT83-07075 (Box 37, Folder 3-4)
      - Filipino Task Force On AIDS: CT83-10341 GF (Box 37, Folder 5)
      - Filipino Task Force On AIDS: CT83-10341A GF (Box 37, Folder 6)
      - Genesis Church: Ecumenical Center: CT83-07097 CARE-F (Box 37, Folder 7)
      - Genesis Church: TAN: CT83-10323A GF (Box 37, Folder 8)
      - Glide Foundation: AIDS Project: CT83-10331 GF (Box 37, Folder 9-10)
      - Haight-Ashbury Free Clinic: CT83-10309 GF (Box 37, Folder 11)
      - Hartford St. Zen Center: CT83-17146 CARE-S (Box 37, Folder 12)
      - Health Outreach Team: CT83-07106 CARE-F (Box 37, Folder 13)
      - Hispanic Headquarters: CT83-10322 GF (Box 37, Folder 14)
      - Home Care Companions, Inc.: CT83-07109 CARE-F (Box 37, Folder 15)
      - Instituto Familiar de la Raza: CT83-07090 CARE-F (Box 37, Folder 16)
      - Japanese Community Youth Council: CT83-00329A GF (Box 37, Folder 17)
      - Larkin St. Youth Center: CT83-07149 CARE-F (Box 37, Folder 18)